[
  {
    "question": "What is 7 + 8?",
    "choices": {
      "a": "15",
      "b": "19",
      "c": "12",
      "d": "5"
    },
    "correct": "a",
    "explanation": "7 + 8 equals 15."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 8 + 9?",
    "choices": {
      "a": "17",
      "b": "8",
      "c": "9",
      "d": "20"
    },
    "correct": "a",
    "explanation": "8 + 9 equals 17."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 + 2?",
    "choices": {
      "a": "9",
      "b": "3",
      "c": "12",
      "d": "5"
    },
    "correct": "a",
    "explanation": "7 + 2 equals 9."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 6 + 1?",
    "choices": {
      "a": "2",
      "b": "7",
      "c": "18",
      "d": "19"
    },
    "correct": "b",
    "explanation": "6 + 1 equals 7."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 9 + 5?",
    "choices": {
      "a": "14",
      "b": "8",
      "c": "17",
      "d": "19"
    },
    "correct": "a",
    "explanation": "9 + 5 equals 14."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 + 5?",
    "choices": {
      "a": "11",
      "b": "5",
      "c": "10",
      "d": "20"
    },
    "correct": "c",
    "explanation": "5 + 5 equals 10."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 + 7?",
    "choices": {
      "a": "10",
      "b": "12",
      "c": "20",
      "d": "17"
    },
    "correct": "b",
    "explanation": "5 + 7 equals 12."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 6 + 6?",
    "choices": {
      "a": "9",
      "b": "4",
      "c": "12",
      "d": "19"
    },
    "correct": "c",
    "explanation": "6 + 6 equals 12."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 5 + 1?",
    "choices": {
      "a": "6",
      "b": "5",
      "c": "20",
      "d": "18"
    },
    "correct": "a",
    "explanation": "5 + 1 equals 6."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 8 + 3?",
    "choices": {
      "a": "20",
      "b": "11",
      "c": "7",
      "d": "6"
    },
    "correct": "b",
    "explanation": "8 + 3 equals 11."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 2 + 1?",
    "choices": {
      "a": "13",
      "b": "15",
      "c": "3",
      "d": "5"
    },
    "correct": "c",
    "explanation": "2 + 1 equals 3."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 + 4?",
    "choices": {
      "a": "11",
      "b": "12",
      "c": "15",
      "d": "10"
    },
    "correct": "a",
    "explanation": "7 + 4 equals 11."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 + 5?",
    "choices": {
      "a": "19",
      "b": "12",
      "c": "6",
      "d": "15"
    },
    "correct": "b",
    "explanation": "7 + 5 equals 12."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 + 9?",
    "choices": {
      "a": "2",
      "b": "6",
      "c": "10",
      "d": "16"
    },
    "correct": "d",
    "explanation": "7 + 9 equals 16."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 7 + 1?",
    "choices": {
      "a": "9",
      "b": "8",
      "c": "11",
      "d": "7"
    },
    "correct": "b",
    "explanation": "7 + 1 equals 8."
  }
]
